<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>The Dark Arts</title><link>https://xeroxxhah.github.io/blog/</link><description>Recent content on The Dark Arts</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 09:18:34 +0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://xeroxxhah.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>6u4rd</title><link>https://xeroxxhah.github.io/blog/project/6u4rd/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 09:18:34 +0500</pubDate><guid>https://xeroxxhah.github.io/blog/project/6u4rd/</guid><description>README.md 👋 6u4rd Your backdoor for your device. It is a simple utility when it is up and running; you get an email every hour with a unique link. You are presented with a hideous dashboard; you can control your device using this dashboard.
Don&amp;rsquo;t ask me why i did it (._.).
Installation &amp;amp; Usage: Follow these steps: 1st: git clone https://github.com/Xeroxxhah/6u4rd.git 2nd: cd 6u4rd 3rd: pip install -r requirements.txt 4th: Setup Dummy Account (Gmail) 5th: Get ngrok token 5th python3 6u4rd.</description></item><item><title>About Me</title><link>https://xeroxxhah.github.io/blog/me/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 07:59:31 +0500</pubDate><guid>https://xeroxxhah.github.io/blog/me/</guid><description>Muhammad Nauman Azeem Rawalpindi,Pakistan nomanazeem@gmail.com @xeroxxhah Education 2019-2023 (expected) BS, Information Tecnology: Bahria University (Islamabad) FYP title: Traffic Generation Framework for IoT Devices
2017-2019 Secondry Education: Hamza Army Public College (Rawalpindi) Experience Penetration Tester self employeed
2019
Bug Bounty Penetration Tester Intern VaporVM IT Services
OCT 2021 - JAN 2022
Security Configuration Assessment Mobile Application Pentesting Web Application Pentesting Infrastructure Security Assessment Python Scripting Penetration Tester Zeroxinn PVT LTD
2020 - Present</description></item><item><title>A New Beginning</title><link>https://xeroxxhah.github.io/blog/posts/2023/a-new-beginning/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 07:41:04 +0500</pubDate><guid>https://xeroxxhah.github.io/blog/posts/2023/a-new-beginning/</guid><description>With each passing day, the world becomes more and more digital. From online shopping to social media, our daily lives are intricately connected to the internet. While the benefits of this digital world are undeniable, it also poses new and unique security challenges. In today&amp;rsquo;s world, cyber security has become an issue of paramount importance, as cyber criminals are constantly finding new ways to steal sensitive information, compromise systems and cause damage to individuals and organizations alike.</description></item></channel></rss>